All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I will be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Horty Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict and find themselves in the midst of an all-out war.
After a change of plans, Horty threatens to crush the entire island under the weight of a massive ship.
Oh!
What's wrong?
It's...
There...
Look!
Horty!
He can still stand?
I can breathe!
I can't stand?
I can still stand, I can still stand?
Oh!
He can still stand while he can still stand!
The final decisive battle against Horty!
Coming to an end! The final decisive battle against Hordy!
If he's this tough, his bounty would be high. Like a hundred million!
He must be hurt.
I'm not letting you interfere, Straw Hat. Not a chance in hell. The Noah will fall. Just try to get those vile human hands on it.
There's nothing you can do now. This is the day Fishman Island dies!
Second gear! Now Gum Gum! Jet Pistol!
Hey queer air strangler!
You're too star!
Ah!
Poor Starhead.
You're too slow!
Oh no, Luffy!
Please don't die!
Yeah!
Gung-Gung!
Jet-Bung-Gung!
That won't stop me!
Armament!
Pardon me!
This is it!
Yes!
Now Gung-Gung!
Run home!
Huh?
Section 9
RRR!
RECa- chosen соус
Dia 2
Hehehe!
Ugh!
T K!
Uh SELE!
Ah!
Cheh explicaré!
Haha!
Don't you worry.
Ah, don't you worry. If those don't hurt enough, I can always make another set.
Damn! How strong can this guy get?
That Red Hawk would have wiped the floor with him before!
After all of this, my power still surprises you!
Come now, Straw Hat. It was granted to me by Heaven to vanquish humans, especially the likes of you!
You were so confident you could gain the advantage once you were able to breathe freely.
But it wasn't enough. No mortal can best the power of the Divine.
I've surpassed the strength of man and fish-man. No one can stop my revenge!
Hordy... He must have mutated far beyond his physical limit by now.
His anger towards humans, combined with the energy steroid, has transformed him into a true monster.
I hope Straw Hat knows what he's up against.
Be careful.
Luffy's losing.
Do you think, maybe, Hordy is really undefeatable?
The situation with the Noah is increasingly dire.
The ship continues to fall steadily toward Fishman Island.
And right now, on the deck, Luffy and Hordy are locked in a fight to the death!
We're about to re-crime!
There must be something we can do!
The Monstrual Hat!
Hear that? Sounds like our captain's got the upper hand.
We really were chosen by the heavens.
Our cause was the right one all along.
Your leader is tough for a human, but he's reached his limits.
His odds of pulling through this are laughable.
No.
Hmm?
As I told you, I have faith in our captain.
Luffy won't be beaten.
I can feel it deep in my bones.
You can die laughing if you like, but you're still finished!
Chopper!
Are you sure you're okay over there?
Oh yeah.
I got it all under control.
With just one Rumble Ball, I can fight in this form for three minutes.
Plus, I don't pass out at the end or anything like that.
Now you guys don't have to look out for me so much.
Don't sell yourself short!
If you can do this kind of stuff whenever you want, you're going to be the one looking out for us!
Flattery will get you nowhere, buddy!
Doesn't work on me!
Ha!
Nope, not at all!
That's creepy!
Don't leave me!
Now you've really made me angry!
I don't care how big you are! All it takes is one good dosin' and you're out of here!
Dosin' all you want? Sorry, but I don't plan on going anywhere.
Now, bring it on!
Nice going.
Yeah! You think you can just chat it up with your friend in the middle of a fight?
You're lucky I don't gnaw straight through you.
I don't know why your straw hat pals bother putting up with dead weight like you.
I'm gonna do my favor and put you out of your misery!
You're welcome to try, but first I want to show you something cool.
Pay attention! You're about to see a magic trick you'll never forget!
A special move? If that's your game, I've got plenty of those myself.
Maybe the squid spear didn't work.
But I've got another weapon that'll cut through anything you can throw at me!
Huh?
Say hello to the Light Bright Spear!
It's powerful enough to cut a hole through your cockpit!
This battle will be over in one shot, but it'll be won by me here!
That does look pretty sweet!
But if I'm being honest, it's still way less ultimate than my ultimate weapon!
You're squid out of luck now, dude!
What's a swordman without his swords?
What should I do?
If you're just gonna croak like a frog, I'm done. Waste of time.
Huh?
Maybe I am a little like a frog.
The kind whose poison's enough to kill a man.
Wrapped this up, you said?
Not till I'm good and ready!
You think I got all puffed up just to deal with a loser like you?
Quit dreaming!
You know, all I gotta do is roll around this plaza a few times and all your friends will be smushed flat as pancakes!
Are you even listening?
Sorry, I was lost in thought.
You were ignoring me!
Uh-huh, trying to think of recipes for big hideous blowfish.
What'd you say?
Alright, that's it!
I'm rolling!
Luffy!
How about you?
He's bleeding!
Poor Luffy!
You don't know when to quit, do you?
Here you are on the brink of death that you continue to stand against me!
Just surrender!
Spare yourself the indignity!
I told you before!
Didn't you hear me?
I'll save Shirahoshi!
And this island!
Oh, Luffy!
Because I promised my friend!
Straw Hat!
Go ahead!
I'll protect them!
Every last one!
Come on!
You humans can be so arrogant it amazes me!
You're more likely to get yourselves killed than admit how weak you are!
So I'll have to beat some humility into you!
Look, I'm kind of in a hurry!
Can we finish this up already?
No!
You humans can be so arrogant it amazes me!
You're more likely to get yourselves killed than admit how weak you are!
So I'll have to beat some humility into you!
Look, I'm kind of in a hurry!
I'm in a hurry!
Can we finish this up already?
If you think you can, be my guest!
Wipi Hoshi, get out of here!
Right!
Fishman Jujutsu!
Water hot!
Shark Hat Go!
Not fast enough!
Now die!
It can't be!
Please no!
Look!
V Saintyvict2
Hebord
Winty!
jobs
Winty?
Third gear!
Armament hardening!
How much does it take?
Insolent fools!
Come come!
Help me come!
It's no use.
Human strength will never stop me!
I will have my revenge,
even if it's the last thing I do!
Shut up!
I've had enough of you!
Crush them.
Noah.
Kill them all.
They've forsaken their brightest fishmen.
They deserve to pay the price.
Yeah.
Huh?
Oh, my God!
Come come!
Call of them!
This is my space, you washed up, pile of bones.
Take a look at my eyes!
This is my space, you washed up pile of bones.
Take one step inside this circle, and you'll be dead all over again.
I promise.
Your move.
I'm terribly sorry, but I've already made my way inside the circle and cut you.
Also, as a fair warning, this will be cold.
Huh? When did you get in here?
Song of Scratches.
Blizzard Slice.
And now a haiku.
A blood-chilling wind howls from the land of the dead.
Send skirts a-flutter.
Gotcha!
What is this?
My green star, human-drake technique.
Those plants have arms and leg-shaped roots that attack and latch onto whatever flies over them.
Yeah!
Good luck with that.
Roargh!
Yeah, yeah, now works!
Green star trampolia.
It's pretty self-explanatory.
Anyway, now that you've been catapulted into the sky, there's not much you can do to defend yourself.
Here goes.
Green star.
I don't care about your dumb dog.
I'll rip it to shreds.
I wouldn't.
See that red bulb on its nose?
If you attack, that thing will release a devastating shockwave three meters wide.
Like this.
Ahhhh!
Like this?
AHHHHHH!
It's packed wolf!
Awesome, right!
Dosen!
Better watch out, or you'll get hit by the doosenest dosen that ever dosered!
PAPARA HAMMER!
No bad!
MOSELE PAUSE!
It...
Groxen...
Eka, eka, eka!
Too bad!
You won't make dried squid out of me!
Frankie!
Eka, eka, eka!
RADICAL THIE!
NILIZOR!
WHOA!
Huh?
It's got a laser beam too!
BANANAS!
RADICAL THIE!
kas
Hold on! Did he just bring a leak?!
All these airs gonna come out!
Enjoy the view. It's your last.
Ah! Hey, you know how to fly!
You scared the guts out of me!
The last two years were a stain upon my soul.
Ooh, Sanji!
I went through hell! It isn't fair!
He's on fire!
I wanna burn those days to ashes!
Hell memory!
Scared the guts out of you?
Good, that'll make the job easier.
Blowfish guts are toxic.
You have to take that part out.
Let's see you block this!
Quit it, Frog. This is over.
I told you I'm not a frog!
I'm the master swordsman, Yozo!
Fishman Island's champion of the octopus, eight-sword style!
Curgatory.
What do you get me?!
My mistake.
Maybe you're not a frog after all.
But you didn't croak.
He did it!
Strawhead beat him!
Finally!
Horny is down!
He did it!
Strawhead beat him!
Finally!
Horny is down!
Even if Luffy can defeat Horty, the Noa will continue its descent as if possessed by the fishman's grudge.
As the islanders stare upon it, they are seized with despair.
Luffy puts his life on the line to break apart the legendary vessel, but it will take more than that to save the island.
On the next One Piece, stop, Noa! Desperate Elephant Gatling! I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!